snapfinger.com 2017-12-02

# Snapfinger Privacy Policy

Effective Date November 7, 2016)

#### This Privacy Policy applies to the sites and app where it appears.

This policy describes how we treat personal information on the mobile apps and websites where it appears (the “Platforms”). By interacting with us, you consent to these practices.

This privacy policy applies to how Snapfinger uses your information. Snapfinger collects information on behalf of restaurant clients. For these clients we provide ordering services. You should also read the restaurant’s privacy policy to understand how they will use your information.

#### We collect information from and about you.

**We may collect contact information and personal information on the Platforms.** For example, we may collect your address when you use the Platforms. We also collect your name, phone number and email address if you register with us.

**We may collect information about your device and Internet usage.**. If you use the Platforms, we might collect information from your phone. We may also collect information about the parts of our Platforms you use or third party apps or websites you visit when you leave our Platforms. We may work with third parties who collect information about you when you use our app.

**We collect payment information.** For example, we collect your credit card number if you make a purchase.

**We may collect other information.** For example, we may collect your location using GPS, a cellular network location, Wi-Fi networks, browser services, or information you provide. We might look at how often you use the Platforms.

#### We collect information in different ways.

**We collect information directly from you.** For example, we collect information if you register on the Platforms.

**We collect information from you passively.** For example, we may collect information from your phone, like your UDID. Our vendors might also use scripts or other tools to track your activities on our Platform. They may do this to make sure our Platforms function properly.

**We may get information about you from third parties.** For example, our business partners or restaurant clients may give us information about you. If our Platforms have social media integration, social media platforms may also give us information about you.

**We combine information.** For example, we may combine information that we have collected offline with information we collect online. Or we may combine information we collect on behalf of one restaurant and with information we’ve collected on behalf of another restaurant. We may also combine information we collect from you with information we receive from third parties.

#### We use information as disclosed and described here.

**We use information to administer the Platforms.**

**We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** For example, we might use your information to respond to your customer feedback. We use payment information to process your transaction.

**We use information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.** We may contact you about our account or feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our app Terms.

**We use information to improve our products and services.** We may use your information to make our website and products better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us.

**We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites.

**We use information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might provide you with information about new products and special offers from this restaurant or others in the Snapfinger network. We might also use your information to serve you ads about products and offers. We might tell you about new features or updates. These might be third party offers or products we think you might find interesting. This includes information from other restaurants with platforms administered by us. If you register with the restaurant, we’ll enroll you in the restaurant’s email newsletter. To manage this, read the choices section below. We may also use push notifications on our mobile apps.

**We use information as otherwise permitted by law.**

#### We may share information with third parties.

**We will share information with our business partners.** For example, we will share information with our restaurant client(s) and their vendors who perform services on their behalf.

**We will share information with our vendors.** These are third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, we may share information with vendors who send emails for us.

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold, we may share information as part of that transaction.

**We may share information with other third parties.** Those third parties may use the information for their marketing purposes or share it for the marketing purposes of others.

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

#### You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.** To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions.

**You can control cookies and tracking tools.** Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies or other tracking tools. How you do so depends on the type of tool. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies. To control flash cookies, which we may use on certain websites from time to time, you can go here. Why? Because flash cookies cannot be controlled through your browser settings.

**Our Do Not Track Policy: Some browsers have “do not track” features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform. We do not currently respond to those signals.** If you block cookies, certain features on our sites may not work. If you block or reject cookies, not all of the tracking described here will stop.

**You can control tools on your mobile devices.** For example, you can turn off the GPS locator or push notifications on your phone.

#### Your California privacy rights.

If you reside in California, you have the right to ask us one time each year if we have shared personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please send us an [email](mailto:privacy@snapfinger.com) at privacy@snapfinger.com, or write to us at the address listed below. Indicate in your letter that you are a California resident making a “Shine the Light” inquiry.

#### These sites and apps are not intended for children.

Our Platforms are meant for adults. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can [email us](mailto:privacy@snapfinger.com) privacy@snapfinger.com. You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries “COPPA Information Request.” Parents, you can learn more about how to protect children"s privacy on-line here.

#### We store information in the United States.

Information we maintain may be stored both within and outside of the United States. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your information to the United States. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country.

#### We use standard security measures.

The Internet and mobile apps are not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our Platforms will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using apps and the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. To learn more about how to protect yourself online, visit www.ftc.gov.

We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

#### We may link to other sites or have third party services on our Platforms we don’t control.

Our Platforms may have links to websites we do not control. Our Platforms may also have plugins or host other third party services that we don’t control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites or third parties. When you interact with those websites or third parties, they may collect information from you. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.

#### Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please email us at privacy@snapfinger.com.

You can also write to us or call at: Snapfinger, Inc., 3025 Windward Plaza, Suite 320 Alpharetta, GA 30005, 678-739-4650.

If you have any questions about this Policy or want to correct or update your information, please email us at [privacy@snapfinger.com](mailto:privacy@snapfinger.com).

#### We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website (www.snapfinger.com) and app. Please check our website and app periodically for updates.

© 2016 Snapfinger, Inc. All rights reserved.
